<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TestingApp</string>
    <string name="Title">This is my testing app</string>
    <string name="Enter">Enter Page 2</string>
    <string name="Enter2">Enter Page 3</string>
    <string name="Page2">These financial calculators will assist you in bringing your money under control and help it grow</string>
    <string name="Page3">This is Page 3</string>
    <string name="EmergencyFund">Emergency Fund</string>
    <string name="CreditCard">Credit Card Repayments</string>
    <string name="CompoundInterest">Compound Interest</string>
    <string name="Irregular">Irregular Payments</string>
    <string name="ccIcon">This is the icon for going to Credit Card repayment preface</string>
    <string name="emergencyIcon">This is the icon for going to Emergency Fund preface</string>
    <string name="compoundIcon">This is the icon for going to Compound Interest preface</string>
    <string name="IrregularIcon">This is the icon for going to Irregular Payments preface</string>
    <string name="EmergencyFundPreface">Emergency Funds are a great way to ensure you do not run out of money if you temporarily lose a job, get sick or need some money for a replacement car.
        This doesn't replace a savings account, and you are not supposed to touch this until you are really in an emergency. </string>
    <string name="CreditCardPreface">Paying off credit card debt is a geat step to being more financially secure. Make note of your interest rate and principal amount.
    The more you pay off the principal, the less interest you get charged.</string>
    <string name="CompoundInterestPreface">Credit cards utilise compound interest to their advantage. You too can utilise compound interest.
        With this calculator, you will be able to see just how much your money can grow.</string>
    <string name="IrregularPreface">Irregular payments are often categorised as payments that happen once per year. It is common to forget that car registration is due at a particular part of the year.
    This calcuator helps you budget by taking the overall amount and breaking it down so you can budget the entire amount over the year instead of trying to find a lump sum once a year.</string>
    <string name="OkButton">OK</string>
</resources>